### Eric M. Ruthig

1712 Foudray Cir S, Avon, IN 46123

312-809-0809

iam@ericruthig.com

## **Professional Summary**

I have been involved in the field of Massage Therapy for the last eight years as a Licensed Massage Therapist (IL) and a Certified Massage Therapist (IN). I returned to school to study the field of Web Development and am now looking for an opportunity to grow in a new field.

Professional History
Indy Massage Company -- Indianapolis, IN
Certified Massage Therapist
November 2016-Present
Responsibilities include performing massage therapy and room cleaning.

Soothe -- Indianapolis, IL
Licensed Massage Therapist
April 2014-Present
Responsibilities included performing in-home massage therapy and travel.

Sauganash Wellness Center -- Chicago, IL Licensed Massage Therapist June 2014-September 2016 Responsibilities included performing massage therapy and room cleaning.

#### Education

Eleven Fifty Academy -- Fishers, IN
Web Development - Gold Badge - Graduated 2021

Pacific College of Oriental Medicine -- Chicago, IL Massage Therapy Certificate -- Graduated 2013

Covenant Christian High School -- Indianapolis, IN Academic Diploma -- Graduated 2002

#### Skills & Related

ABMP Member #1062780 - Spanish (fluent) - Hot Stone Certified - Cupping Certified

# **Professional References**

Alli Padrick	Owner, Indy Massage Company	317-910-9354
April Emmons	Owner, Indy Massage Company	317-454-4165
Rachel Shaffer	Owner, Sauganash Wellness Center	630-670-7366